https://www.greeleystampede.org/privacy-terms-cookies

skip to main content
Privacy, Terms & Cookies
The Greeley Stampede is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy rights when visiting any
page of our website, www.greeleystampede.org. To protect your Personal
Information, the Greeley Stampede has created the guidelines outlined below,
which explain the kinds of information the website collects, how it is used,
the conditions under which it is made available to third parties, how
information is maintained and our compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy
Act. Your use of the website indicates your acceptance of and agreement with
the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.
Information Collected
While visiting the website, we may ask you to provide
information that personally identifies you ("personal information")
for purposes of interacting with the website. Such personal information may
include, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, street address and
e-mail address, age and gender. On any page that collects personal information,
we will specifically describe what information is required in order to provide
you with the product or service or enter you in the promotion you have
requested, as well as respond to your inquiry or comment. This personally
identifiable data is collected by means of form interfaces on our website, into
which the user must voluntarily enter the information requested. If you place
an online order or enter a commercial transaction at this website, we will
collect additional personally identifiable information, including billing
address and credit card information. We may also collect personally
identifiable information through purchase forms, surveys, contests, emails we
receive from you and your other interactions with our website. You may browse
the website without registering or providing any personally identifying
information.
IP Addresses
This website also collects anonymous data that is not
indicative of and cannot be traced to an individual without the cooperation of
their Internet Service Provider. This data includes information about the
user's remote IP address, referral data (which page "linked" to the
present request) and the browser software's user-agent string. This information
is accepted passively from the HTTP headers that are sent from the user when
requesting any file from the server. The Greeley Stampede does log IP addresses for
systems administration, troubleshooting purposes and to determine website
usage.
Cookies
The website uses "cookies", which are
elements of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be
stored on your system. This element of data is a piece of text, not a program.
The website can only access the information from a cookie sent by the website.
We cannot access other cookies sent by other websites or the information
contained therein. Additionally, we cannot learn your e-mail address or any
other information about you through the use of a cookie. The only way we would
learn such information is if you specifically and voluntarily submit that information
to us, for example, through a registration system, by entering a sweepstakes or
promotion, etc.
Why does the Site use cookies?
The Greeley Stampede uses cookies to track usage of the website and further
personalize your experience when you are visiting the Website. By tracking
usage, we can best determine what features of the website best serve the users.
Overall, the use of cookies helps to give you a more personalized experience at
the website. The information is used to keep our website fresh and relevant to
you, the user. Cookies also allow you to avoid retyping your e-mail address on
the website. The information stored in a cookie is used to allow us to
personalize your experience on the website.
May I decline to accept a cookie?
You may decline to accept cookies sent by the website by selecting an option on
your browser to reject cookies. However, some portions of the website may
require cookies in order to provide you with the full set of features offered.
Cookies enable our server to know that you are a registered user. In addition,
our registration system may require that you accept the cookies from the
website in order to access that portion of the website.
Use of Personal Information
We believe in protecting your privacy and will not share personal information
with third parties outside of the Greeley Stampede, except as described in this
Privacy Policy. We believe that we can enhance your experience on our website
with the information you share with us. We use personal information about you
to improve our advertising and marketing efforts, to statistically analyze
website usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to personalize
the website's content, layout, and services. We also may use your personal
information, such as your e-mail address or mailing address, to contact you
regarding products and/or services that may be of interest to you, to respond
to an inquiry from you regarding the information that we have collected, to
respond to your comments and suggestions and to fill orders and complete
commercial transactions that you initiate with this website.
The Greeley Stampede may match specific and/or aggregated personal information with
third party data to provide you with product and content offerings that
interest you and improve our advertising and marketing efforts. The Greeley Stampede also may disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services
to potential advertisers, partners, other third parties, our affiliate
companies and for other lawful purposes. For example, we provide our
advertisers with aggregate information about our users, such as statistics
regarding the number of website users that view their advertisements.
As part of your experience on our website, you may receive communications from
us related to products and services that might interest you. While we believe
these services will enhance your experience at our website, you will at all
times be able to opt out from receiving these communications, either by
specifically opting out of these services or by deleting your profile from our
database.
We have today, and will in the future, have arrangements with third party
service providers, such as credit card processors, shipping companies, and
fulfillment services, other third-party vendors, or any partner who assists in
the operations and/or administration of this website.
When you sign up for a service we offer on the Website, we may be required to
share personal information with that service provider in order to provide the
service. These third party providers are not permitted to retain or use
personal information for any purpose unrelated to providing the service.
We reserve the right to disclose personal information when needed to comply
with the law or a legal process, cooperate with investigations of purported
unlawful activities, to identify persons violating the law, to investigate or
assist in investigations incident to misuse or abuse of this website, or in
connection with the sale of part or all of the Greeley Stampede.
Party Collecting the Information
Information entered by website visitors is retrieved directly by the Greeley Stampede:
600 N. 14th Ave, Greeley, CO 80631.
This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and dissemination of information
that the website collects from you. To the extent that you disclose any
information to other parties, whether through, for example, online auctions,
chat rooms, personal ads, or the like, through third party services or
promotions offered on or through the website or through other websites
throughout the internet, different policies may apply and the Greeley Stampede
shall not be responsible for the use or dissemination of such information.
Links to Other Materials
Third party sites linked to and from the site are not necessarily under the
control of the Greeley Stampede.  The Greeley Stampede shall have no
responsibilities or liabilities whatsoever for the content or privacy practices
of any such linked site or any link or linking program at any time. The Greeley Stampede
does not necessarily endorse companies (or related products or services) to or
from which the website is linked. If you decide to access any of the third
party sites linked to the website, you do so entirely at your own risk. The Greeley Stampede
hereby disclaims any rights to trademarks, service marks, trade names, logos,
copyrights, patents, domain names or other intellectual property interests of
third parties.
Children's Privacy
The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998
(“COPPA”) applies only to websites of a commercial nature, and while the Greeley Stampede
is a for-profit organization, it considers COPPA to provide sound advice for any
website that is intended for use by children. For this reason, the Greeley Stampede
does not knowingly collect or solicit any personally identifiable information
from children under 13 years of age without verifiable parental consent.
In the event that we receive actual knowledge that we have collected such
personal information without the requisite and verifiable parental consent, we
will delete that information from our database as quickly as is practicable.
With respect to any form interface that appears on a webpage at our website, no
information will be knowingly collected from any user under the age of 13.
Where “age” or “date of birth” is requested on the form interface, no
information will be stored or transmitted unless the response indicates that
the user is 13 years of age or older.
Providing personal information is never a prerequisite for accessing the basic
content or resources on this website.
Maintenance of Personal Information
The personally identifiable information collected at
this website may be indefinitely retained and electronically archived. Please
keep in mind that information collected at this website may be different than
that collected at or through other activities, events, or functions related to the Greeley Stampede
and the use and disclosure, if any, of such information may vary and are not
covered under this policy.
Opting-Out
We respect your privacy and ability to choose whether to share information with
us and any third party. You may choose to "opt-out" of sharing
personal information in several ways. When choosing to use certain features or
services on the website, you can choose whether to share optional personal
information in connection with the feature or service. If you receive
communications from us that you prefer not to receive, you may opt-out from
receiving these communications, either by specifically indicating this
preference in a communication to us via the Unsubscribe link or by deleting
your registration profile from our database. You may also opt-out altogether
from providing personal information to us by not registering on the website and
thereby not providing personal information. You may also choose at a later date
to have your name removed from our database. To do so, please follow the
process described below. Certain portions of the website and certain services
provided on the website, however, do require registration in order to access or
use these areas and services. If you choose not to register or provide certain
information, these areas will not be accessible to you.
Reviewing, Changing and Deleting Your Personal Information
You may access all of the personal information that we
collect from you online and maintain by e-mailing us at Info@greeleystampede.org. To
protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify
your identity before granting access or making corrections.
Security
The Greeley Stampede maintains industry standard encryption technologies to ensure
the security, integrity and privacy of the personal information that you
provide through the website. Please keep in mind, however, that no data
transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be
100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information
you transmit using our website, and therefore, it is important to remember that
you transmit such information at your own risk. The Greeley Stampede does not
assume responsibility for use or disclosure of your information that are the
result of unauthorized or illegal access to our systems or to those of our
vendors or partners.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions or comments about our
Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at info@greeleystampede.org.
Effective Date and Changes
Understanding that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving, any changes to
this policy will be promptly posted on this page, with an updated
"effective date" posted below. The Greeley Stampede reserves the right to
modify the terms of this policy at any time and in our sole discretion, by
posting a change notice to this page. Your continued use of the website
following our posting of a change notice will constitute binding acceptance of
those changes.Refund Policy Refund for merchandise only.  Subject to Stampede approval.  DOES NOT INCLUDE TICKET PURCHASES.
This Privacy Policy was last modified on October 22, 2013.
